pexda.com 2019-06-30

# PRIVACY POLICY – Pexda

**Last Updated on 09/26/2017**

This Privacy Policy applies to [pexda.com](https://pexda.com/) and their sub-domains, owned (collectively, “Pexda”), we place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy and security of our customers and their information. Pexda is committed to maintaining the privacy of personally identifiable information (such as credit card number, tax id, phone number, address and email address) that you provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive when you transmit data to any machine owned by Pexda. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access and update this information. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Pexda does not own or control, or individuals that Pexda does not employ or manage.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at [support@pexda.com](mailto:support@pexda.com).

## COLLECTION & USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect personally identifiable information from you if you request information from us, sign up to join our email lists, register for an account, participate in our promotions, such as contests and sweepstakes, take our surveys, use our products and services, contact us about a purchase, or email, call or otherwise communicate with us.

Information we collect is used to notify you of updates to our websites or any products or services we offer; to respond to your requests or inquiries; to process and complete your transactions, including, as applicable, order confirmation, billing and delivering products or services; to provide you with newsletters, articles, product or service alerts and announcements; to contact you about programs, products or services that we believe may be of interest to you; to share offers from other companies with you; to conduct market research; to analyze transactions and purchase histories to provide you with customized offers and to improve our products, services, programs and other offerings; to verify and validate your identity; to keep records of our interactions with you if you place an order or otherwise deal with our representatives; to prevent, investigate or provide notice of fraud, unlawful or criminal activity, or unauthorized access to or use of personal information, our website or data systems; to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights; and to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide your personally identifiable information to us.

If you purchase or begin to purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email or shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes, to fill your orders, and provide customer service and to solicit additional orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

We may also collect, from you, the following personal information about your contacts (name and address) when shipping a product. When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided.

If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at [support@pexda.com](mailto:support@pexda.com).

## UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Upon request, Pexda will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, you may request the information be corrected, updated, amended, or deleted through our [Contact Us page](https://pexda.com/#contact-1) or by contacting us at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within thirty days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## OTHER ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION

Pexda automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, domain type, browser version, service provider, cookies, and the pages you request. This data is used in the aggregate. Pexda uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, sales and marketing analysis, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes. We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

## COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

Pexda and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

## THIRD PARTY TRACKING

Third parties also use cookies and other tracking technologies on our site, of which data is only collected in the aggregate. The use of cookies by third parties is covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Third parties use session ID and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.

## BEHAVIORAL TARGETING / RE-TARGETING

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites. This information is used to provide you targeted advertising across the internet, based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## MOBILE DEVICE DATA

When users download, install and use Pexda services on their mobile phone or other wireless telecommunications device, Pexda automatically gathers information, including without limitation, carrier providers, unique device identifiers, geo-location information (if allowed by the user), the types of mobile devices accessing the services, and the types of operating systems accessing the services (collectively, “Mobile Device Data”). A unique device identifier is a string of alphanumeric characters (similar to a serial number) used to uniquely identify and distinguish each mobile phone or other wireless communications device. Location services can be enabled or disabled at any time, through the settings on your mobile device. Pexda uses Mobile Device Data to understand usage patterns and to improve our goods, services and functionality of our Sites.

## WHAT AND HOW INFORMATION IS USED

Pexda may contact you about new or existing Pexda products and special offers specific to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you can unsubscribe to our emails by clicking “unsubscribe” within each email. You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow websites to collect personally identifiable information over time about your online activities across different websites or online services. At this time our websites do not respond to the preferences you may have set in your web browser regarding the collection of your information, and our websites may continue to collect information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. We may enable third parties to collect information in connection with our websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, any collection of information by third parties on our websites.

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our most common practices with respect to the disclosure of personal information include the following:

**Consent.**  We may disclose your personal information to third parties with your consent. You may give your consent in several ways, such as through a written agreement that you sign or acknowledge; an online method, such as a “click through” agreement or registration page; through a mobile application which you install on your mobile device or by enrolling in a text alert program; or through the terms and conditions under which we provide you a particular product or service. Sometimes your consent may be implied. For example, if you purchase products with a credit card and have them shipped to your home, you implicitly consent to the disclosure of your name and address to a third-party shipping company to complete the delivery, and of your credit card number to the credit card processor to authorize the transaction and to the bank to collect payment.

**Affiliated Businesses.**  We may share your personal information with our parent or affiliated businesses, joint venturers or promotion partners, for their use in a manner similar to the purposes described in this Policy.

**Agents/Service Providers.**  We use third party service providers to assist us in providing our services and websites, including database backup providers to protect our data, and a fraud prevention service. We may disclose your personal information to third parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf or for your benefit. We may also utilize the services of third parties to verify customer data, or to supplement other information we have collected. We may also contract with third parties to host a site, conduct market research, or send you information regarding our products or services or those of other companies with whom we conduct business. All service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide their respective services to us.

**Marketing.**  We may send offers to selected groups of our customers on behalf of other businesses. We also may disclose the personal information we collect to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. Such marketing may include, without limitation: (i) contacting you to complete purchases that you initiated but did not complete; and (ii) contacting you to purchase additional or related product to those you previously purchased. Upon request, Pexda will provide a list of categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes, and the third parties to whom such information has been disclosed, in the preceding 12 months. You may contact [support@pexda.com](mailto:support@pexda.com) to receive this information, and Pexda will provide it within 30 days.

**Legal Process.**  We may disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

**Certain Business Transfers.**  Your personal information may be disclosed as part of a corporate business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, joint venture, or financing or sale of company assets, and could be transferred to a third party as one of the business assets in such a transaction. It may also be disclosed in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership. We will use reasonable efforts to direct any such transferee to use your personal information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.

You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

## SECURITY

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using SSL.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

The information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, or provide customer service.

## BLOGS

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or open forum on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there may be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog, testimonials or community forum, contact us at [support@pexda.com](mailto:support@pexda.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## TESTIMONIALS

We display customer testimonials on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@pexda.com](mailto:support@pexda.com)

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

If you click on a link to a third party site you will leave our site and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as us. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

## SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by submitting your inquiry to our email [support@pexda.com](mailto:support@pexda.com)
